

BLOCKCHAIN DEVELOPER

Details

Lakeview &, N Country Club
Stillwater, 74074
United States
617-300-7891
anjinhuaguru@outlook.com

DATE OF BIRTH

1987-10-01

Links

Linkedin

Twitter

Skills

Solidity

Node.js

Blockchain

React

JavaScript

Languages

English

Chinese

Profile

Hello

I am working a Blockchain developer since 2016 and I have many experiences in the skills.

Smart Contract, Dapp, Defi, PoW(PoS) networks, etc).

I worked on several NFT projects and smart contract development, I have enough skill, knowledge for them.

Thank

Employment History

Software Developer, assured Techmatics, Doral

MARCH 2016 - MAY 2018

Website development, Rest API, Web application development

I worked in the role of company website build and manage and track API for truck movement.

Web Developer, motorcyclepartz, Doral

MARCH 2014 - AUGUST 2018

Web Developer

Blockchain Developer, RChain Tech, Beijing

JANUARY 2016 - MARCH 2021

https://www.linkedin.com/company/rchain-tech

There I worked several company-related jobs and in there include this work role.

High-performance crypto exchange development(IEO) and ICO, STO smart contract & manage panel development

EVM and another blockchain network hard fork and PoS, PoC network development

Smart Contract Developer, Roaring Leaders, New York City

NOVEMBER 2020 - JULY 2021

In EVM config NFT project's smart contract development & Audit.

Minting Dapp page build and utility token create and community tech skills

https://linktr.ee/roaringleaders

Education

Tsinghua University, Beijing

APRIL 2008 - OCTOBER 2012

Computer Software Engineer

Yeshiva & Misivta Tiferes Elimelech

References

Jimmy from Callffry

Courses

Certified Enterprise Blockchain Professional

Blockchain Talents Labs Course

Extra-curricular activities

Online Store Development, Shopify

Online Store Development

Online Store Development, Bigcommerce & Woocommerce